<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gnits Eve</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="msg"><![CDATA[>Artista under the agies of LINC GNITS named Artista is inagurated on 25th january 2015.  > Artista organsise Galleria where the arts of Gnits students are exhibited.  > A campus poised on sheer scientific thrills requires a balancing dose of art so that aesthetics and beauty around us are not forgotten.  > The motto of the Artista is to inspire and enable our students to actively learn and develop their talent and skills that will develop artistic expression.  > Artista Club gives our students a boarder view of art and many forms like Painting, Poster Designing, Clay Modeling, Collage, Cartooning, Pencil Drawing etc.]]></string>
    <string name="vivekananda_msg"><![CDATA[> To establish a social work presence on campus through acts of advocacy, research, education and volunteerism  > To promote a positive image of the social work profession  > To encourage its members to assume responsibility for identifying the need for social change and actively participate in facilitating such changes  > To support and nurture the personal and professional development of its membership]]></string>
    <string name="club"><![CDATA[> The club offers a competing platform for the knowledge-hungry students.  > It promises to cultivate a passion for quizzing, Debating, creative writing, literature, Elocution, etc.,. among the students.  > Literary club is to develop self-efficacy and confidence and would help to enhance the general knowledge base.  > Works in tandem to benefit students in the disciplines of writing and speaking by conducting events that are both instructional and enjoyable.  > It develops excellent communication skills and teaches students to think spontaneously.]]></string>
    <string name="csi">Computer Society of India is the first and largest body of computer professionals in India.[citation needed] It was started on 6 March 1965 by a few computer professionals and has now grown to be the national body representing computer professionals. It has 72 chapters across India, 511 student branches, and 100,000 members.[2]
        The Computer Society of India is a non-profit professional meet to exchange views and information learn and share ideas. The wide spectrum of members is committed to the advancement of theory and practice of Computer Engineering and Technology Systems, Science and Engineering, Information Processing and related Arts and Sciences.
        The Society also encourages and assists professionals to maintain integrity and competence of the profession and fosters a sense of partnership amongst members. Besides the activities held at the Chapters and Student Branches, the Society also conducts periodic conferences, seminars.
        Through the initiatives of Professor Rangaswamy Narasimhan the first President, CSI has been in close liaison with International Federation for Information Processing (IFIP) since its inception in 1965, when observers from India attended the IFIP Council meeting. Since 1974, when CSI became a member of IFIP, CSI has organized many IFIP sponsored events and was host to the 1978 Council meeting in Bombay and 1988 General Assembly in New Delhi. It represents India in technical committees and working groups of IFIP.</string>
    <string name="cybersurds">Cyber suds is estlablished in the year 2005.Under cybersurds,CSE depatment regulerly organizes Rangoli,Logo Design,Poster Presentation,Mehendi Design,Tech crossword,Paper presentation,Debugging contest,paper presentations skill test
    ,generating concept for the given set of pictures etc to update the knowledge and skills for students
    in their feilds of activity to become top quality professionl engineers and technicians needed by the industry and other organisations</string>
    <string name="iete">The Institution Of Electronics. And Telecommunication Engineers (IETE) Student Chapter is a Technical Association of ECE department focused at driving the students towards improving their technical prowess. It was established in the year 2003.</string>
    <string name="technoboom">Technoboom is an IT Department Students Association that is being monitored by Mrs.M.Bhavani and Mrs.S.Vaishnavi. This club provides the students a platform to showcase their talents. Many Technical and Non-Technical events are conducted so as to provide the students with some extracurricular activities. An event is conducted every week and students are persuaded to participate in the events, the main goal of these activities is to help the students discover themselves, to develop leadership qualities, to understand how to work in a team, acquire skills, become competent, to learn time management and also to become proficient. These activities are mainly aimed at training the students to face any challenge they are confronted with in the mere future. This is a process of teaching the values in a friendly manner. Finally the winners of the events are encouraged by giving them prices on the main day i.e., Traditional Day of IT Department.</string>
    <string name="mindspark">Mindspark is a student founded and managed club of ECE Department GNITS for promoting the need for the practical implementation of the conventional academics with emphasis on the fields of robotics and Electronics. Founded in the year 2017, the club is still in its exploring stages of development. We as a club, also represented the college in various national symposiums including the annual fest of NITs. We strive to take the club forward and hope to encourage practical, application oriented learning more.</string>
</resources>
